Guide to the Stanford Campus Recreation Association Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Campus Recreation Association records
1961-1999
SC0797
Stanford Campus Recreation Association.
1.75 Linear feet
Records include minutes, by-laws, financial records, correspondence, memos, proposals, reports, announcements, and newsletters.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Stanford Campus Recreation Association (SCRA) was organized in 1961 and opened their facilities in 1962 with a swimming pool and tennis courts.
Description of the Collection
Records include minutes, by-laws, financial records, correspondence, memos, proposals, reports, announcements, and newsletters.
Access Terms
Stanford Campus Recreation Association.; Recreation centers --California --Stanford.; Swim clubs.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-2005-379
  - Volume 1: Committees, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Volume 1: By-Laws, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Volume 1: Minutes, 1961-62 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Volume 1: Finances, 1962-62 and Rules-Operation, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Volume 1: Facilities, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Volume 1: Memberships, 1961-62 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Volume 1: Trustees-President, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Volume 1: Reports to Members, 1961-62 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Volume 1: Similar Developments (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Volume 1: Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Volume 2: Minutes, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Volume 2: Minutes, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Volume 2: Minutes, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Volume 2: Minutes, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Volume 2: Minutes, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Volume 2: Minutes, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Volume 2: Minutes, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Volume 2: Minutes, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Volume 2: Minutes, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Volume 2: Minutes, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Volume 2: Minutes, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Volume 2: Minutes, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Volume 2: Minutes, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Volume 3: Minutes, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Volume 3: Minutes, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Volume 3: Minutes, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Volume 3: Minutes, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Volume 3: Minutes, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Volume 3: Minutes, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Volume 3: Minutes, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Volume 3: Minutes, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Volume 3: Minutes, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Volume 3: Minutes, 1984-85 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Volume 3: Minutes, 1988-89 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Volume 3: Minutes, 1990-91 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Volume 3: Minutes, 1992-94 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Volume 3: Minutes, 1995-98 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Volume 4: SCRA construction/improvement issues, 1963-69 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Volume 4: SCRA history, 1970-86 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Volume 4: letters of resignation, 1962-70 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Volume 4: Annual meeting minutes (1 of 3), 1980-99 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Volume 4: Annual meeting minutes (2 of 3), 1964-79 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Volume 4: Annual meeting minutes (3 of 3), 1962-63 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Volume 4: SCRA Newsletters, 1976-98 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Volume 5: SCRA correspondence with membership (1 of 4), 1963-67 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Volume 5: SCRA correspondence with membership (2 of 4), 1967-71 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Volume 5: SCRA correspondence with membership (3 of 4), 1971-77 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Volume 5: SCRA correspondence with membership (4 of 4), 1977-98 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Volume 5: Annual SCRA financial statements, 1962-84 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Volume 6: Documents and correspondence (1 of 2), 1962-75 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Volume 6: Documents and correspondence (2 of 2), 1962-86 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Volume 6: SCRALET letters, 1996-97 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Volume 6: Profit and loss, 1997-98 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Volume 6: SCRA minutes, 1994-97 (Box 4, Folder 6)